auction123.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy - Auction123.com

This policy covers how Auction123 treats personal information that Auction123 collects and receives, including information related to your past use of Auction123 products/software and services. Personal and business information is information about you that is personally identifiable like your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available.

This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that Auction123 does not own or control, or to people that Auction123 does not employ or manage. In addition, certain companies associated with Auction123, such as eBay, have their own privacy statements that we do not control.

#### Information Collection and Use

Auction123 collects personal and business information when you register with Auction123, when you use Auction123 product/software and services, when you visit Auction 123 pages or the pages of certain Auction123 partners, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. Auction123 may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register we ask for information such as your name, email address, birth date, gender, zip code, occupation, industry, and personal interests. For some financial products and services we may also ask for your address, Social Security number, and information about your assets. You retain the right to refuse to provide any information requested by electing to not complete the registration process.

We ask that children under the age of 18 do not submit any personal information to us, and require all children under the age of 18 to use this Site under the direct supervision of your parent(s) or legal guardian(s).

Auction123 collects information about your transactions with us and with some of our business partners, including information your use of financial products/software and services that we offer.

Using our site to bid, research, sell, or buy items on eBay may require that we securely transmit your eBay username and password directly to eBay's computer systems. By posting feedback, responding to feedback, or using other tools within our website to perform an action connected with your eBay account, you are authorizing us to transmit the provided information to eBay and retain an archive of the transaction on our server. In addition, an authorized representative of eBay may occasionally request your contact information in order to resolve a service issue or dispute. In such cases, the information provided will be limited to contact name(s), telephone number(s) and / or email address(es) associated with your account.

Auction123 automatically receives and records information on our server logs from your browser, including your IP address, Auction123 cookie information, and the page you request. Your Internet service provider may automatically provide information about you to our web server, such as its web site address and possibly your email address. We may collect information that you send to us in an e-mail message or letter and information that you submit to us in a CGI or other script based form. Email sent to us may not be secure. If you choose to send us an email message or letter, you are consenting to our retention of the content of the message, your email or physical address, and our response.

Auction123 uses information for the following general purposes: to fulfill your request for products/software and services, improve our services, provide service and support, notify you online or offline about new offers,services, or updates, collect fees owed, customize your experience, identify and protect our company and assets from fraudulent or otherwise criminal activity,conduct research, and provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the Auction123 service, such as service announcements, and administrative messages, that are considered part of your Auction123 account, without offering you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving them.

Auction123 does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or nonaffiliated companies without your explicit consent except to provide products or services you've requested, or under the following circumstances:

Auction123 may occasionally enlist the services of a third party in order to provide you with the services you have requested (vehicle inspections and condition reports, insurance and shipping, affiliate and rewards programs). In such cases, we may provide some of your personal information directly to the service provider to facilitate effective delivery of your requested services. These third party providers are bound by agreements of confidentiality that prohibit their use of your personal information provided by us for any purpose outside of delivery of the services that we have outsourced to them. Any additional information provided by you to an internal service provider is at your discretion, and governed in accordance with their privacy policy and terms of use.

In order to protect consumers and businesses, Auction123.com cooperates with law enforcement agencies and inquiries. When requested by a verified law enforcement or government official in relation to an alleged illegal activity or criminal investigation, you authorize us to disclose your name(s), mailing and billing address(es), telephone number(s) and email address(es), and Auction123.com UserID(s) and comprehensive history of activity on our Site(s) without a subpoena. Auction123 may also respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or turn over other personal information to exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims;

With respect to the constant evolution of international, national, and local regulations, we cannot ensure that your information and communications will never be disclosed or intercepted in ways not outlined within this Policy. We use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, but we do not promise (nor should you expect) that information intended to remain private will always remain so.

We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of Auction123 terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

Auction123.com may share some or all of your personal information with another business entity in the event that we are acquired by that business entity, have plans to merge with, or actually merge with that business entity. In this event, we may notify you but are not required to do so, before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Auction123 may display targeted advertisements based on personal information. Advertisers may assume that people who interact with, view, or click on targeted ads meet the targeting criteria - for example, women ages 18-24 from a particular geographic area.

Auction123 does not provide any personal information to the advertiser when you interact with or view a targeted ad. By interacting with or viewing an ad, however, you are consenting to the possibility that the advertiser will make the assumption that you meet the targeting criteria used to display the ad.

#### Cookies

Certain pages of our Site may employ or access "Cookies" as a tracking mechanism of our promotion and marketing efforts, to analyze the flow of our website, and conduct other analysis as needed. Certain features on our website may require the use of a cookie.

Auction123 may let other companies that show advertisements on some of our pages set and access their cookies on your computer. Other company's use of their cookies is subject to their ownprivacy policies, not Auction123's. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to Auction123's cookies.

Auction123 may use web beacons to access Auction123 cookies inside and outside our network of web sites and in connection with Auction123 product and services.

#### Confidentiality and Security

We limit access to personal information about you to employees and independent contractors who we believe reasonably need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs. Your information is stored on Auction123.com servers located in the United States. We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you. Fool-proof security on the Internet, however, cannot be guaranteed, nor does it exist.

#### Changes to this Privacy Policy

Auction123 may update this policy. We may notify you about significant changes in the way we treat personal information by sending a notice to the primary email address specified in your Auction123 account or by placing a prominent notice on our site. Changes to the privacy policy will be automatically effective when posted on the site or notification has been sent.

#### Questions and Suggestions

If you have questions or suggestions, email us at:  
[[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#c292b0abb4a3a1bb92adaeaba1bb8283b7a1b6abadacf3f0f1eca1adaf)

or call us Toll FREE at:  
888.514.0123
